[
    {
        "question": "Teddy ____________ of moving closer to the city centre.",
        "options": [
            "A. thinks",
            "B. is thinking",
            "C. don’t think",
            "D. aren’t thinking"
        ],
        "answer": "B. is thinking"
    },
    {
        "question": "We ____________ giving you a lift home.",
        "options": [
            "A. don’t mind",
            "B. aren’t minding",
            "C. doesn’t mind",
            "D. isn’t minding"
        ],
        "answer": "A. don’t mind"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Potters ____________ to Dubai at 9:00 tomorrow morning.",
        "options": [
            "A. is flying",
            "B. don’t fly",
            "C. doesn’t fly",
            "D. are flying"
        ],
        "answer": "D. are flying"
    },
    {
        "question": "____________ is your favorite European city?",
        "options": [
            "A. When",
            "B. How",
            "C. Which",
            "D. Who"
        ],
        "answer": "C. Which"
    },
    {
        "question": "____________ much do they charge for a single room with breakfast?",
        "options": [
            "A. How",
            "B. Who",
            "C. What",
            "D. Where"
        ],
        "answer": "A. How"
    },
    {
        "question": "____________ is your brother talking to?",
        "options": [
            "A. When",
            "B. Who",
            "C. Whose",
            "D. How"
        ],
        "answer": "B. Who"
    },
    {
        "question": "The teacher ____________ believe his excuse for not coming to school yesterday.",
        "options": [
            "A. didn’t",
            "B. don’t",
            "C. used to not",
            "D. use to"
        ],
        "answer": "A. didn’t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bobby ____________ skinny when he was a child.",
        "options": [
            "A. was used to",
            "B. were",
            "C. used to be",
            "D. got used"
        ],
        "answer": "C. used to be"
    },
    {
        "question": "____________ to contact Mr. Peterson twice, but didn’t find him.",
        "options": [
            "A. tried",
            "B. tries",
            "C. used to try",
            "D. try"
        ],
        "answer": "A. tried"
    },
    {
        "question": "After a couple of days, Sam finally ____________ up early in the morning.",
        "options": [
            "A. used to wake",
            "B. get used to wake",
            "C. wake",
            "D. got used to waking"
        ],
        "answer": "D. got used to waking"
    },
    {
        "question": "It took him a month to recover ____________ his illness.",
        "options": [
            "A. for",
            "B. from",
            "C. of",
            "D. at"
        ],
        "answer": "B. from"
    },
    {
        "question": "The book exhibition took ____________ at the Carlton Hotel.",
        "options": [
            "A. part",
            "B. advantage",
            "C. it easy",
            "D. place"
        ],
        "answer": "D. place"
    },
    {
        "question": "I didn’t ____________ Jason to come on time.",
        "options": [
            "A. expect",
            "B. remember",
            "C. wait",
            "D. reminded"
        ],
        "answer": "A. expect"
    },
    {
        "question": "I’m sorry but I can’t find it ____________ the map.",
        "options": [
            "A. over",
            "B. on",
            "C. between",
            "D. along"
        ],
        "answer": "B. on"
    },
    {
        "question": "They spent the whole day in Alexandria looking at the ____________.",
        "options": [
            "A. tasks",
            "B. part",
            "C. jobs",
            "D. sights"
        ],
        "answer": "D. sights"
    },
    {
        "question": "He was lucky to find that ____________ in their law firm.",
        "options": [
            "A. job",
            "B. work",
            "C. site",
            "D. task"
        ],
        "answer": "A. job"
    },
    {
        "question": "I think that these trainers belong ____________ your brother.",
        "options": [
            "A. on",
            "B. in",
            "C. to",
            "D. at"
        ],
        "answer": "C. to"
    },
    {
        "question": "They usually take ____________ of what I tell them.",
        "options": [
            "A. their time",
            "B. part",
            "C. place",
            "D. no notice"
        ],
        "answer": "D. no notice"
    },
    {
        "question": "We never argue ____________ our teacher.",
        "options": [
            "A. with",
            "B. at",
            "C. at",
            "D. from"
        ],
        "answer": "A. with"
    },
    {
        "question": "This dish is very healthy because it consists ____________ fish and vegetables.",
        "options": [
            "A. on",
            "B. of",
            "C. at",
            "D. with"
        ],
        "answer": "B. of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tim ____________ the news, while his son was playing computer games.",
        "options": [
            "A. is watching",
            "B. watches",
            "C. was watching",
            "D. watching"
        ],
        "answer": "C. was watching"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lenny ____________ his old house two months ago.",
        "options": [
            "A. were selling",
            "B. sells",
            "C. is selling",
            "D. sold"
        ],
        "answer": "D. sold"
    },
    {
        "question": "He didn’t meet Joe and Alf, because they left ____________ than they usually do.",
        "options": [
            "A. early",
            "B. earlier",
            "C. earliest",
            "D. the earliest"
        ],
        "answer": "B. earlier"
    },
    {
        "question": "__________ you finish your report on time?",
        "options": [
            "A. Was",
            "B. Are",
            "C. Did",
            "D. Were"
        ],
        "answer": "C. Did"
    },
    {
        "question": "I was resting all day yesterday, because I was ____________ tired.",
        "options": [
            "A. terrible",
            "B. most terrible",
            "C. terribly",
            "D. more terribly"
        ],
        "answer": "C. terribly"
    },
    {
        "question": "Robert was crossing the street when he ____________ Fred riding a motorcycle.",
        "options": [
            "A. saw",
            "B. was seeing",
            "C. seeing",
            "D. is seeing"
        ],
        "answer": "A. saw"
    },
    {
        "question": "This artist is ____________ famous of all three that you mentioned.",
        "options": [
            "A. the less",
            "B. least",
            "C. less",
            "D. the least"
        ],
        "answer": "D. the least"
    },
    {
        "question": "That’s the boy ____________ father is our teacher.",
        "options": [
            "A. who",
            "B. which",
            "C. whose",
            "D. that"
        ],
        "answer": "C. whose"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you tell me ____________ to put these boxes?",
        "options": [
            "A. where",
            "B. when",
            "C. which",
            "D. who"
        ],
        "answer": "A. where"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mark, ____________ is only twenty, teaches French.",
        "options": [
            "A. which",
            "B. who",
            "C. when",
            "D. whose"
        ],
        "answer": "B. who"
    },
    {
        "question": "My doctor advised me to ____________ a sport.",
        "options": [
            "A. take off",
            "B. take after",
            "C. take up",
            "D. take on"
        ],
        "answer": "C. take up"
    },
    {
        "question": "I can’t believe that they ____________ your offer.",
        "options": [
            "A. turned on",
            "B. turned off",
            "C. turned out",
            "D. turned down"
        ],
        "answer": "D. turned down"
    },
    {
        "question": "When I suggested a walk in the woods, he ____________.",
        "options": [
            "A. credited",
            "B. nodded",
            "C. raised",
            "D. shook"
        ],
        "answer": "B. nodded"
    },
    {
        "question": "After his mother’s ____________, he moved to Argentina.",
        "options": [
            "A. death",
            "B. strength",
            "C. power",
            "D. impression"
        ],
        "answer": "A. death"
    },
    {
        "question": "It was really ____________ that nobody was hurt in that accident.",
        "options": [
            "A. strong",
            "B. powerful",
            "C. incredible",
            "D. truthful"
        ],
        "answer": "C. incredible"
    },
    {
        "question": "Both my children are afraid ____________ the dark.",
        "options": [
            "A. of",
            "B. for",
            "C. on",
            "D. with"
        ],
        "answer": "A. of"
    },
    {
        "question": "They did everything in their ____________ to keep the company.",
        "options": [
            "A. truth",
            "B. strength",
            "C. impression",
            "D. power"
        ],
        "answer": "D. power"
    },
    {
        "question": "I bought a leather bag that ____________ my new boots.",
        "options": [
            "A. match",
            "B. matches",
            "C. suits",
            "D. suit"
        ],
        "answer": "B. matches"
    },
    {
        "question": "Both her children have a very vivid ____________.",
        "options": [
            "A. description",
            "B. impression",
            "C. admiration",
            "D. imagination"
        ],
        "answer": "D. imagination"
    },
    [
        {
            "question": "I’ve got the ____________ that they’re lying again.",
            "options": [
                "A. impression",
                "B. admiration",
                "C. imagination",
                "D. description"
            ],
            "answer": "A. impression"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Carltons have never _________ Denmark before.",
            "options": [
                "A. been to",
                "B. gone to",
                "C. gone in",
                "D. been at"
            ],
            "answer": "A. been to"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you __________ thought of studying abroad?",
            "options": [
                "A. since",
                "B. before",
                "C. never",
                "D. ever"
            ],
            "answer": "D. ever"
        },
        {
            "question": "Danny __________ tennis since he was a child.",
            "options": [
                "A. played",
                "B. plays",
                "C. been playing",
                "D. has been playing"
            ],
            "answer": "D. has been playing"
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been raining heavily __________ our plane took off two hours ago.",
            "options": [
                "A. while",
                "B. already",
                "C. since",
                "D. still"
            ],
            "answer": "C. since"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mr. Marfin __________ go on business trip very often.",
            "options": [
                "A. need",
                "B. needs",
                "C. doesn’t have",
                "D. has to"
            ],
            "answer": "B. needs"
        },
        {
            "question": "We can’t meet Jack today. We __________ to work overtime.",
            "options": [
                "A. have",
                "B. must",
                "C. had better",
                "D. would rather"
            ],
            "answer": "B. must"
        },
        {
            "question": "I’d __________ join you for dinner than stay at home.",
            "options": [
                "A. rather",
                "B. had better",
                "C. need",
                "D. must"
            ],
            "answer": "A. rather"
        },
        {
            "question": "Luckily, we __________ wait for them. We can leave right now.",
            "options": [
                "A. don’t have",
                "B. don’t need",
                "C. needn’t",
                "D. not have to"
            ],
            "answer": "C. needn’t"
        },
        {
            "question": "She __________ still be at home. I talked to her on the phone a couple of minutes ago.",
            "options": [
                "A. has to",
                "B. better",
                "C. must",
                "D. needs"
            ],
            "answer": "C. must"
        },
        {
            "question": "I __________ see an optician. I can’t see very clearly lately.",
            "options": [
                "A. would rather",
                "B. may not",
                "C. might not",
                "D. had better"
            ],
            "answer": "D. had better"
        }
    ]
]